Now obviously in this course we built a couple of different applications, to be precise
we built an application with server side rendered views and that includes the possibility to return
just html pages or as we did it, to use a templating engine like ejs and obviously we build two APIs,
.
we built a rest API and a grapghql API.
Now how do we deploy these two types of applications,
one with views and one without views?
First of all we have to keep in mind that how the application behaves, what it does with incoming requests
and which data it accepts and returns, this is all our logic,
this is all code we wrote. In the end when we look at it from a technical perspective,
in both kinds of applications, we start a normal node server and we use a node framework,
in this case the most popular one, express and therefore these types of applications have the same hosting
requirements.
We don't have to make a difference here because in the end when we move our code to a web server, then
there we also just want to do the exact same thing we did locally. We'll start our node server and wait
for incoming requests and therefore we don't have to differentiate between these kinds of applications,
when it comes to deployment we simply deploy our code, start the node server and we are good to go.